fusionbeads.com 2019-03-16

# Privacy Policy, Fusion Beads

Last updated: March 11, 2019

Fusion Beads, Inc. ("Fusion Beads," "we," "our," "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to our website at www.fusionbeads.com (the “website”) and not to any websites of third parties, which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering, use, storage, and dissemination practices of the website. We are committed to not sharing your Personal Information (defined below) with advertisers or spammers. 

Your use of our website, registration on our website, or your providing to us any content or personal information constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, which are incorporated herein by reference. If you do not understand the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, do not agree to be bound by the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, or if your jurisdiction will not honor them, you must immediately leave the website and refrain from using it.  

Each time you use the website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply.

## 1\. Changes to Terms and Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice to you. We will generally provide notice of changes by posting a new version on our website and/or by a change notice on the website. It is your responsibility to review the Terms and Privacy Policy periodically. If at any time you find either unacceptable, you must immediately leave the website and cease using it. You will be deemed to have agreed to any such change by your continued use of the website following the date of the change.

## 2\. What Information about Customers Does Fusion Beads Gather?

Fusion Beads may collect information about you from a variety of sources, including information we collect from you directly and information we collect about you when you visit our website or view our online advertisements. 

Information we collect directly from you:

We collect information directly from you when you register with our site, participate in our offers, promotions, purchase products from our site, or otherwise provide information directly to us. We collect Personal Information, along with other types of information, on the website. “Personal Information” means information that, alone or in combination with other information, can be used to identify or contact an individual and may include, but is not limited to:

  * Name, email address, postal address
  * Month and day of birth
  * Username and password
  * Telephone number
  * Gift recipient name and email address
  * Payment information (e.g., credit card information)
  * Information you make public in portions of the website that are open to any viewer, such as our Community

This Personal Information can be combined with other types of information to identify or contact an individual, including combining it with interests, hobbies, photos, your brand preferences, your Facebook, Twitter or other social media handles, your geographic location if you are accessing the Site from a GPS-enabled mobile device, any other personal profile or account information you choose to submit through our website, and (if applicable) your company name and business contact information. 

Information we collect when you visit our website or view our online advertisements:

We use cookies and other technologies to collect information about you when you visit our website or view our online advertisements. The following are examples of information we may collect with these technologies: 

  * Your browser type, operating system, and IP address
  * General advertising and usage analytics
  * Web pages you view
  * Links you click
  * The website you visited before coming to our website
  * Fusion Beads emails you open and/or forward
  * Fusion Beads offers or links you connect to via emails and/or online advertisements

If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, you should set your browser to refuse cookies before accessing this website, with the understanding that certain features and/or services may not function properly without the aid of cookies. If you refuse cookies, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality. 

You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain parts of the website, receiving certain services, making purchases, and/or participating in sweepstakes, giveaways, and other promotions. 

Fusion Beads’ uses third-party services providers to help administer its Rewards Program and payment-processing. These third-party services providers may also collect Personal Information from you, including credit, debit, or other billing account information. While you may always choose not to provide Personal Information to such third-party service providers, this may prevent you from receiving certain services, including the Rewards Program and any transaction involving online payment. 

We may also collect non-Personal Information (aggregate, non-individually identifiable or demographic information). An example of non-Personal Information is system-related information such as IP addresses, click-through and other website use information, browser and browser speed, bandwidth of your Internet connectivity, general location of your server and the pages of our website that were viewed during a visit. 

We may use other standard Internet activity tracking technologies, such as web beacons and similar technologies, to track your use of our website or our ad content. A web beacon is a programming code used to display an image on a web page and can also transfer an individual’s user identification to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about the individual. Web beacons collect only limited information, which includes a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. Such information may be used in targeted or behavioral advertising. We may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters or online advertisements to determine whether messages have been opened or acted upon. We may use the information we obtain in this manner to customize our services, ad content, and offers we provide to users via our website, to deliver targeted advertisements through such vehicles, and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming, or other activities. We may also carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any Personal Information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular campaign. 

Like most web sites, we use web server log files. Records in our log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service providers (ISP's), referring pages, exit pages, platform types, and date/time stamps. We use web server log files to administer the site, to provide broad traffic information for site planning purposes, and to ensure that our terms of service agreement is being adhered to. IP addresses are not tied to personally identifiable information in our web server log files.

## 3\. How does Fusion Beads Use Customer Information?

Fusion Beads does not sell, trade, or rent your Personal Information to others. This information is for our private records only. We may, however, allow advertisers to request that their advertisements be directed at certain users (e.g., users in a certain geographic location, or age, gender and / or with certain interests). In the event that you interact with a certain advertisement, the advertiser (or the company with which the advertiser works, for example, its ad agency or an advertising network) may determine certain characteristics about you. 

Fusion Beads may use Personal Information to: market our products and services to users; set up and manage user accounts; improve online operations; process transactions (for example, any credit, debit or other billing account information collected from you will only be used to process transactions requested by you); carry out our obligations arising from any contracts or other arrangements entered into between you and us; send text messages and notifications to your cell phone to inform you about special offers; provide customer service; send users newsletters, RSS feeds, and/or other communications or services that you have signed up for or otherwise agreed to receive (for example, messages about special offers); display content customized to your interests or preferences (for example, we may target you with select custom ads, messages and offers, basing our selections on information you provide); send account- or transaction-related communications such as welcome letters and transaction confirmations; perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so; manage our systems; keep our website safe and secure; and notify you about changes to our products or services. 

We may only use your Personal Information in the ways we specified when it was collected (including as described in this Privacy Policy). We may use your non-Personal Information (including but not limited to Personal Information that has been de-identified and/or aggregated) for any reason in Fusion Beads’ sole discretion. Any geolocation data collected from your mobile device may also be used for the purpose of delivering customized services and ads. However, advertisers will not have direct access to your location and will not be able to view your location on a map. We may share broadly aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. An example of this kind of information is the number of pages served each day, week, or month. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information in any way. In order to effectively manage the website, your non-Personal Information (including, without limitation, de-identified, aggregated Personal Information) may be disclosed to partners and advertisers to facilitate account-related activities, including our Rewards Program, manage and improve our website, and serve relevant advertisements to you. In addition, we may disclose Personal Information and non-Personal Information to employees, companies, agents, contractors, service providers or others engaged to perform functions on our behalf (such as processing of payments, processing of Rewards Program transactions, provision of data storage, hosting of our website, marketing of our products and services, conducting audits, and performing web analytics). We may also disclose non-Personal Information to our clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers, and other third parties if we deem such disclosure, in our sole discretion, to have sound business reasons or justifications. 

If you choose to use our social networking function to post information to Facebook, Twitter or another social networking site, anyone who has access to your information through that other site will be able to see your information. 

If you provide feedback on any of our products and services, we may use your feedback for any purpose. We will collect any information contained in your communication and will treat the information in the communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may disclose your information if we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to: (a) enforce or apply the terms and conditions of the website, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements or an enforceable governmental request, (c) protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users, or other third parties, (d) prevent a crime or protect national security, or (e) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues.. We may also use and disclose your information in connection with a contemplated reorganization or reorganization of our business, in connection with financing or a sale or other transaction involving the disposal of all or part of our business or assets, including for the purpose of permitting the due diligence required to assess whether to proceed with a transaction. 

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is interrupted for a prolonged period we might send all users an email message. Users cannot opt-out of this type of messages, though they can deactivate their account. In response to a user's direct inquiry, we will send an email to provide assistance with the user’s account or their use of the website. 

## 4\. Children

We do not intentionally gather personal information about visitors to our web site who are under the age of 18. We only offer the web site to persons 18 years of age and older. If you are a parent or legal guardian and learn that your child has provided us with his or her personal information, we ask that you contact us and we will delete that information.

## 5\. Security of Customer Information

Fusion Beads takes every reasonable precaution to protect our users' sensitive information ̶ including Personal Information and payment information ̶ from loss, theft, copying, unauthorized disclosure, use, or modification. When users submit sensitive information via the website, that information is protected both online and off-line. 

When you place orders, we provide the use of a secure server, which is compliant with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI). The secure socket layer (SSL) protocol encrypts the information you input before it is sent to the web server. We then retrieve all orders using an encrypted connection, ensuring the safety of your personal and credit card information. All customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

We use a 256-bit encryption SSL certificate through Symantec to ensure the highest level of security when you place orders with us. SSL provides secure communication by combining the following two elements: 

Authentication 

\- A digital certificate is tied to a specific domain, and a certification authority (an independent and trusted third-party company - ours is Symantec) performs a number of checks to confirm the identity of the organization requesting the certificate prior to issuing it. In this way, the certificate may only be installed on the domain against which it has been authenticated, providing users with the assurance they need. 

Encryption 

\- Encryption is the process of transforming information to make it unintelligible to all but the intended recipient. This forms the basis of data integrity and privacy necessary for e-commerce. 

We also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need to see the information to perform their jobs are allowed access. The servers that store personally identifiable information are located in a secure environment in a locked facility. Regular backups of private information are kept under lock and key. All employees are briefed regularly on our privacy policy and practices. 

Technical safeguards (including, but not limited to, dedicated firewall computers, passwords, and encryption) are in place to minimize as much as possible the disclosure of sensitive and private user information. We also limit staff access and their ability to enter or view information in the website based upon their role in your case. 

Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its security. You are responsible for keeping the user name and password you use for accessing our services confidential. We ask you not to share it with anyone. 

When you use our website on your computing device, your information may be stored locally on that device as well. We cannot guarantee the security of such locally-stored information. 

We reserve the right to retain information collected about you indefinitely for business, legal, or tax purposes. However, we strive to retain this information for only as long as it is necessary for the above purposes, and to destroy it afterwards to prevent unauthorized parties from gaining access to this information. 

Despite the precautions we take to protect the information you share on our website, we recommend that you not place sensitive information, such as account numbers and passwords, on FusionBeads.com. Like most online services, we cannot fully guarantee the safety and privacy of such information, whether Personal Information, non-Personal Information, payment information, or other types of information. In addition, we strongly recommend that you do not re-use an existing password as the password for your FusionBeads.com account. 

## 6\. Controlling Your Personal Information

When you use our website, we make a good faith effort to provide you with access to your Personal Information and to either correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We provide a way for users to update their Personal Information on our website. Alternately, users can send an email to support@fusionbeads.com and request updates or changes to Personal Information. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected, or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backups), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case, where we provide information access and correction, we generally perform this service free of charge. However, if doing so would require disproportionate effort, we may charge a fee to cover the cost of verifying the application and locating and retrieving, reviewing, and copying any material requested. 

Please be aware that if you delete your Personal Information, you may not be able to continue to use the website. Also, even if you request that we delete your Personal Information, we may need to retain certain information for a limited period of time to satisfy our legal, audit, and/or dispute resolution requirements. 

## 7\. Third Party Websites

Our website may provide links to or advertisements from other websites that are operated by third parties, such as organizations, businesses, and merchants. We provide these links for your convenience and we do not endorse such websites, their contents, or their privacy policies. We have no control over and do not review these websites, their content, or their privacy policies. Under no circumstances will Fusion Beads be responsible or liable, whether directly or indirectly, for any loss caused or allegedly caused by these other websites, including, without limitation, their content, the goods and services offered by them, their privacy policies, or your reliance on them. We have not investigated, monitored or checked these other websites for accuracy, completeness, or conformance with applicable laws and regulations. If you leave this website and access these other websites, you do so at your own risk, and the rules and policies of the other websites, including their privacy policies, will apply to you while you are on their websites. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of service of those websites so that you understand how those websites collect, use, and share any Personal Information.

## 8\. CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS' PRIVACY RIGHTS

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business with whom the California resident has established a business relationship the following information: (1) the categories of information that Fusion Beads disclosed to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year; (2) the names and addresses of third parties that received such information; and (3) if the nature of a third party's business cannot be reasonably determined from the third party's name, examples of the products or services marketed, subject to certain exceptions. You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you individually. To exercise your rights, you may make one request each year by emailing us at support@fusionbeads.com. Be sure that your request provides enough information to properly identify you. 

## 9\. Business Transitions

Fusion Beads reserves the right to sell or transfer information (including your Personal and non-Personal Information) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of our company, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or receivership of our business, and you hereby consent to any such sale or transfer. If any such transfer is required, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you in writing in advance by posting a notice on the website and/or emailing you at your contact email address of record, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the transferee will continue to use any Personal Information collected from you prior to the transfer in accordance with the terms of the then-current version of this Privacy Policy. 

## 10\. How you can Stop Receiving Communications from Us

When you receive communications from us, including email, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us by following the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in the e-mail you receive, or by contacting us directly. Once you have submitted your e-mail address to unsubscribe, please note that you may continue to receive emails for a short time while our system updates your request.

You may change any of the personal information in your account by editing your Account information.

Rewards Program Communications; Opt-In Required. Enrollment in the Rewards Program does not automatically sign Members up for Fusion Beads Rewards Program emails or other Fusion Beads offers and promotional emails. Members must separately opt in to receive these emails.

## 11\. How you can Reach Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, to request access to your personal information in our records, or the correction of that information, or to opt out of receiving information as permitted under this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Fusion Beads 13024 Stone Ave. N. Seattle, WA 98133

By phone: 1-888-781-3559

Email: support@fusionbeads.com
